# **Giacomo Cecchinato**

Current Location: Padova, Italy Nationality: Italian Date of Birth: 22/05/1986 Phone: +39 3401777634

**Email (preferred):** giacomocecchinato@libero.it **Web:** https://gcecchinato.github.io/giacomo-cecchinato/



# **Experience**

### .Net Developer - Eulogika s.r.l.

I work as a software developer for a 1-10 person software house.

Most relevant activities are:

- Winform application for data acquisition and analysis for foundries: development, bugfix, first installation, updates
- Asp.core app for trade certificates: development and bugfix back and front end
- Winform app as an Erp for small businesses (mainly Pcb manufacture)
- Winform app to import data from csv, txt or any database into sqlserver databases

To summarize: winform applications (80%) asp.net/asp.core(20%).

Tools: C#, Visual Studio, Devexpress, Entity Framework, Ling, Sql Server, SSMS, Svn, Wrike.

# .Net Developer - Ict4Btb s.r.l.

Worked for a year as a consultant for Ovs S.p.a.

Development and bugfix of winform applications for sales forecast.

Tools C#, Visual Studio, Devexpress, Linq, DB2,TFS, Citrix

# .Net Developer - Clesp s.r.l.

Support in the development of the company winform app. Erp.

Tools C#, Devexpress, Svn, SSMS

### Web Developer Intern - Omitech s.r.l.

Development of website in WordPress. Development of mvc application in Ruby on Rails.

Tools: WordPress, Html, Css, Ruby On Rails, MongoDB

Help Desk Technician - Sanità Regione Veneto

Jan 2015 - Jan 2016 1 Year

Sep 2014 - Dec 2014

Sep 2010 - Sep 2013

Nov 2016 - Nov 2017

Aug 2016 - Nov 2016

Mar 2016 - June 2016

1 Year

3 Months

3 Months

# **Education**

# **Basic Course on Java, C# and Web Development**

Msc. in Bioengineering - Università degli Studi di Padova

Thesis Title: "Analysis of sets of three consecutive residues for interface identification". Elaboration (made in Java) of output parameters obtained by molecular analysis software. Implementation of an algorithm (made in R) for the identification of crucial features for the

generation of protein bonds. Final Grade: 92/110

#### Bsc. in Biomedic Engineering - Università degli Studi di Padova

Biomedical Engineering

Thesis: "Structural and anatomical analysis of the forefoot". Final Grade: 92/110

Sep 2005 - Sep 2010

#### **Skills**

**Daily Use Tools:** .Net Framework: 4.5 - 4.8, C#, Winform Apps, Asp Core Apps, Sql Server: 2008/2014/2017/2019, Sql, Visual Studio: 2013-2022, Devexpress: 17-21, Svn, TeamViewer, Vnc, Wrike

**Less Used/Minor or Personal Projects:** Html & Css, Javascript, Wpf, basic knowledge of Plc, WordPress, MySql, Git, Tfs, Java, Eclipse, Matlab, Python, R, Linux/Ubuntu, Ruby On Rails, Qlik

### Language

English: fluent

Italian: mother tongue

German: basic knowledge (A1-A2)

## About me

Looking for a job as .Net Web developer/Winform developer.

Nice empathic guy, I'm trying to improve my software development skills and IT knowledge to reach a "senior" level. Some of my interests: football, padel, gym, trekking, ps4, music, history, movies, learning German, finance

Nov 2017 - Present 4+ Years